http://www.meyerkreuzer.com/privacy-policy

Call for a Free Consultation
630-871-1002
WHEATON | CHICAGO | OSWEGO
HomeFirm OverviewAttorneysAndrew P. CoresMatthew GrobWendy M. MusielakAnnette K. CorriganRobin C. SlatteryPractice AreasCollaborative Law and MediationCollaborative LawWhat Is the Collaborative Law Process?Collaborative Versus Traditional LitigationMediationWhy Choose Mediation? How Mediation WorksConflict ResolutionCourt-Appointed Versus Private MediationFamily LawCohabitation AgreementsDomestic Partnerships Fathers' Rights Grandparents’ RightsGuardian Ad LitemGuardianshipsMothers' RightsPaternityPostnuptial AgreementsPrenuptial AgreementsDivorceAn Amicable DivorceAttorneys Fees in a DivorceBankruptcy & Divorce Contested Versus Uncontested DivorceDissipation of Marital Assets Dividing Marital DebtDivision of PropertyDivorce MediationGrounds for Divorce in IL Legal SeparationLong-Term Maintenance/AlimonyMilitary Divorce Protecting Credit During DivorceSocial Media and DivorceSpousal SupportThe Divorce ProcessChild Custody / Parental ResponsibilitiesChild RelocationChild Visitation / Parenting TimeCreating a Parenting PlanFactors in Deciding Child CustodyJuvenile Rights in Child CustodyParenting Agreements Parental RelocationChild Support Child Support in High-Income FamiliesModification of Child Support Orders * 2017 and 2016 Family Law ChangesHigh Asset and Complex DivorceComplex DivorceBusiness Valuation LitigationComplex Property Division Financial Restraining OrdersFinding Hidden AssetsHigh-Asset Maintenance/AlimonyInvestment & Retirement Accounts in DivorceProtecting Professional Practices The Business Valuation ProcessPost Divorce Issues
Enforcement of Court OrdersModification of Child Custody OrdersModification of Divorce JudgmentsModification of Spousal SupportResourcesAwards & MembershipsFirm NewsLegal ArticlesUsing Collaborative Law to Resolve Family Legal IssuesUnconventional penalty for late child support payees gaining momentumTips to Protect Your Credit During and After DivorceThe Basics on the Enforceability of Premarital Agreements in IllinoisSeparate Lives - One Roof: Divorced Roommates Common in IllinoisProtecting Your Family-Owned Business During a DivorceProposal to Change Child Visitation Standards in IllinoisPrenuptial Agreements Becoming Essential Part of MarriageNew program targets overdue child support paymentsModern Blended FamiliesLeaving Marriage Behind: Many Couples Deciding to Remain UnmarriedEnforcement of Illinois Prenuptial AgreementsDivorce and Facebook: Be Careful What You PostDiscovering Hidden Assets During DivorceConsiderations for divorced parents seeking to relocateConcerns Regarding High-Asset and Complex DivorcesCohabitation: Economic Benefits and DrawbacksBaby boomer divorce rates increasing, financial planning vitalVideosBlogReviewsContactWheaton OfficeOswego Office
Toggle navigation
Privacy Policy
HomeFirm OverviewAttorneysAndrew P. CoresMatthew GrobWendy M. MusielakAnnette K. CorriganRobin C. SlatteryPractice AreasCollaborative Law and MediationCollaborative LawWhat Is the Collaborative Law Process?Collaborative Versus Traditional LitigationMediationWhy Choose Mediation? How Mediation WorksConflict ResolutionCourt-Appointed Versus Private MediationFamily LawCohabitation AgreementsDomestic Partnerships Fathers' Rights Grandparents’ RightsGuardian Ad LitemGuardianshipsMothers' RightsPaternityPostnuptial AgreementsPrenuptial AgreementsDivorceAn Amicable DivorceAttorneys Fees in a DivorceBankruptcy & Divorce Contested Versus Uncontested DivorceDissipation of Marital Assets Dividing Marital DebtDivision of PropertyDivorce MediationGrounds for Divorce in IL Legal SeparationLong-Term Maintenance/AlimonyMilitary Divorce Protecting Credit During DivorceSocial Media and DivorceSpousal SupportThe Divorce ProcessChild Custody / Parental ResponsibilitiesChild RelocationChild Visitation / Parenting TimeCreating a Parenting PlanFactors in Deciding Child CustodyJuvenile Rights in Child CustodyParenting Agreements Parental RelocationChild Support Child Support in High-Income FamiliesModification of Child Support Orders * 2017 and 2016 Family Law ChangesHigh Asset and Complex DivorceComplex DivorceBusiness Valuation LitigationComplex Property Division Financial Restraining OrdersFinding Hidden AssetsHigh-Asset Maintenance/AlimonyInvestment & Retirement Accounts in DivorceProtecting Professional Practices The Business Valuation ProcessPost Divorce Issues
Enforcement of Court OrdersModification of Child Custody OrdersModification of Divorce JudgmentsModification of Spousal SupportResourcesAwards & MembershipsFirm NewsLegal ArticlesUsing Collaborative Law to Resolve Family Legal IssuesUnconventional penalty for late child support payees gaining momentumTips to Protect Your Credit During and After DivorceThe Basics on the Enforceability of Premarital Agreements in IllinoisSeparate Lives - One Roof: Divorced Roommates Common in IllinoisProtecting Your Family-Owned Business During a DivorceProposal to Change Child Visitation Standards in IllinoisPrenuptial Agreements Becoming Essential Part of MarriageNew program targets overdue child support paymentsModern Blended FamiliesLeaving Marriage Behind: Many Couples Deciding to Remain UnmarriedEnforcement of Illinois Prenuptial AgreementsDivorce and Facebook: Be Careful What You PostDiscovering Hidden Assets During DivorceConsiderations for divorced parents seeking to relocateConcerns Regarding High-Asset and Complex DivorcesCohabitation: Economic Benefits and DrawbacksBaby boomer divorce rates increasing, financial planning vitalVideosBlogReviewsContactWheaton OfficeOswego Office
Privacy Policy
This privacy policy applies to information collected online from users of this website. In this policy, you can learn what kind of information we collect, when and how we might use that information, how we protect the information, and the choices you have with respect to your personal information.
What personal information is collected through this website and how is it used?
We collect information about our users in three ways: directly from the user, from our Web server logs and through cookies. We use the information primarily to provide you with a personalized Internet experience that delivers the information, resources, and services that are most relevant and helpful to you. We don't share any of the information you provide with others, unless we say so in this Privacy Policy, or when we believe in good faith that the law requires it.
User-supplied information: If you fill out the contact form on this website, we will ask you to provide some personal information (such as e-mail address, name, phone number and state). We only require that you provide an e-mail address on the contact form. Further, if chat is available through this site, you may be asked to provide information if you participate in an online chat. Please do not submit any confidential, proprietary or sensitive personally identifiable information (e.g. Social Security Number; date of birth; drivers license number; or credit card, bank account or other financial information) (collectively, “Sensitive Information”). If you submit any Sensitive Information, you do so at your own risk and we will not be liable to you or responsible for consequences of your submission.
Information that you provide to us through the contact form or an online chat will be used so that we may respond to your inquiry. We may also use information you provide to us to communicate with you in the future. If you do not wish to receive such communications, you may opt out (unsubscribe) as described below.
Web server logs: When you visit our website, we may track information about your visit and store that information in web server logs, which are records of the activities on our sites. The servers automatically capture and save the information electronically. Examples of the information we may collect include:
your unique Internet protocol address;
the name of your unique Internet service provider;
the town/city, county/state and country from which you access our website;
the kind of browser or computer you use;
the number of links you click within the site;
the date and time of your visit;
the web page from which you arrived to our site;
the pages you viewed on the site; and
certain searches/queries that you conducted via our website(s).
The information we collect in web server logs helps us administer the site, analyze its usage, protect the website and its content from inappropriate use and improve the user's experience.
Cookies: In order to offer and provide a customized and personal service, our websites and applications may use cookies to store and help track information about you. Cookies are simply small pieces of data that are sent to your browser from a Web server and stored on your computer's hard drive. We use cookies to help remind us who you are and to help you navigate our sites during your visits. Cookies allow us to save passwords and preferences for you so you won't have to re-enter them each time you visit.
The use of cookies is relatively standard. Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies. However, if you prefer, you can set your browser to either notify you when you receive a cookie, or to refuse to accept cookies. You should understand that some features of many sites may not function properly if you don't accept cookies.
How is personal information protected?
We take certain appropriate security measures to help protect your personal information from accidental loss and from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. However, we cannot guarantee that unauthorized persons will always be unable to defeat our security measures.
Who has access to the information?
We will not sell, rent, or lease mailing lists or other user data to others, and we will not make your personal information available to any unaffiliated parties, except as follows:
to agents, website vendors and/or contractors who may use it on our behalf or in connection with their relationship with us;
if we are unable to assist with your matter, but know an unaffiliated attorney or firm that may be able to help you, we may refer you and share information you provided us with that party; and
as required by law, in a matter of public safety or policy, as needed in connection with the transfer of our business assets (for example, if we are acquired by another firm or if we are liquidated during bankruptcy proceedings), or if we believe in good faith that sharing the data is necessary to protect our rights or property.
How can I correct, amend or delete my personal information and/or opt out of future communications?
You may opt out of any future contacts from us at any time. Contact us via the phone number, contact form or mailing address on our website at any time to:
see what data we have about you, if any;
change/correct any data we have about you;
ask us to delete any data we have about you; and/or
opt out of future communications from us.
If you have any additional questions or concerns about this privacy policy, please contact us via the phone number, contact form or mailing address listed on this website. If our information practices change in a significant way, we will post the policy changes here.
Effective March 1, 2012
Practice Areas
Collaborative Law and MediationCollaborative LawCollaborative Versus Traditional LitigationKane County Collaborative LawWhat Is the Collaborative Law Process?MediationConflict ResolutionCourt-Appointed Versus Private MediationHow Mediation WorksWhy Choose Mediation?Family LawCohabitation AgreementsDomestic PartnershipsFathers' RightsGrandparents’ RightsGuardian Ad LitemGuardianshipsMothers' RightsPaternityPostnuptial AgreementsPrenuptial AgreementsDivorceAn Amicable DivorceAttorneys Fees in a DivorceBankruptcy & DivorceContested Versus Uncontested DivorceDissipation of Marital AssetsDividing Marital DebtDivision of PropertyDivorce MediationGrounds for Divorce in ILLegal SeparationLong-Term Maintenance/AlimonyMilitary DivorceProtecting Credit During DivorceSocial Media and DivorceSpousal SupportThe Divorce ProcessChild Custody / Parental ResponsibilitiesChild RelocationChild Visitation / Parenting TimeCreating a Parenting PlanFactors in Deciding Child Custody Juvenile Rights in Child Custody Parenting AgreementsParental RelocationChild SupportChild Support in High-Income FamiliesModification of Child Support Orders* 2017 and 2016 Family Law ChangesHigh Asset and Complex DivorceComplex DivorceDuPage County Complex DivorceBusiness Valuation LitigationComplex Property DivisionDuPage County High Asset DivorceFinancial Restraining OrdersFinding Hidden AssetsHigh-Asset Maintenance/AlimonyInvestment & Retirement Accounts in DivorceProtecting Professional PracticesThe Business Valuation ProcessPost Divorce IssuesEnforcement of Court OrdersModification of Spousal SupportModification of Divorce JudgmentsModification of Child Custody Orders
Recent Blog Posts
4 Things to Consider Regarding Disputes Over Parental Responsibilities
Will I Be Ordered to Pay Spousal Maintenance in My Illinois Divorce?
How Do I Know If I Am Ready to Get a Divorce?
Are There Alternatives to Going to Court for My Illinois Divorce?
Is an Illinois Prenuptial Agreement Right for You?
HomeFirm OverviewAttorneysPractice AreasResourcesBlogReviewsContact
Toggle navigation
Privacy Policy
HomeFirm OverviewAttorneysPractice AreasResourcesBlogReviewsContact
DisclaimerSitemapPrivacy Policy
Toggle navigation
Privacy Policy
DisclaimerSitemapPrivacy Policy
Wheaton Office
400 S. County Farm RoadSuite 200 Wheaton, IL 60187
630-871-1002
Oswego Office
123 W. Washington StreetSuite 334 Oswego, IL 60543
630-518-4002
Chicago Office
Appointments Available
Andrew Cores Family Law Group has offices in Wheaton, Chicago and Oswego, and serves clients from those cities as well as through the Chicago area, including: Naperville, Oakbrook, Hinsdale, Lisle, Winfield, Warrenville, Downers Grove, Glen Ellyn, Geneva, St. Charles, Elgin, Batavia, Sugar Grove, Schaumburg, Skokie, Joliet, Plainfield, Lemont, Yorkville, Montgomery, Burr Ridge, Darien, DuPage County, Kane County, Cook County, Will County and Kendall County, Illinois.
Disclaimer|Sitemap|Privacy Policy
© 2020 Andrew Cores Family Law Group | 400 South County Farm Road, Suite 200, Wheaton, IL 60187 | Phone: 630-871-1002
